Hello friends, once again you are
welcome to our channel Share, so if you
like this video then do not forget to like, share and
subscribe and one more thing if
you have not opened a demat account yet
for investment or chatting then you will
find the link in the description of this video, you will find the
Telegram channel link
in the description of this video and
if you have not seen the videos of this trend analysis MSN from my channel then you will get the
link of its video, you will get the picture of this video,
before this the stock
can rise, take the goods, so the name of the company is
ICC Chief General Body Insurance, Safai Se
Lamba General Insurance, it is the best
private sector non-life insurance
company in India, if we talk about skin and dance then there is
still no outstanding stock of negative 535 per cent, if we
talk about returns then there is 20.28 per cent tax, if we
talk about market cap then there is a
market cap of 6300 crores, if we talk about that deal then there is a
dividend yield of 0.5%, if we
talk about 80 then there
is a free fruit of Rs 1125  If we talk about it, it
is of Rs.1626,
you can see from the daily chart that
its next actor is health,
people did not like it very much, it was
beaten badly, you can see that all this
kept going straight from the level of 1600 to 1350, but it stopped after thinking that its first
support is 1350, its next
support is of ₹13100, now its current
price is Rs.1433, if we
talk about its target, then 1620
is its first target and in the long term
you will see it adding Rs.800
within 1 to 2 years, so as you
can see, this fold was coming on the 15th just a few days ago and
now a
little bus stand is seen coming inside it
and its results are also on 17th April, so
MSD line is going to make more police force now, so if
you want, you can invest in it,
you can also see the mode on balance volume, it is
seen rising in the same  In this way, you
can see that there is a slight increase in the money flow in these taxes,
so let's see, it is setting on the seat,
this is also in the ongoing market, this is the
price, you will see it changing after the market closes, the
current
price of 24 is 1424 rupees, its
first part of 1375 rupees, which was invested in it, is
1428, if we talk about its people, then the
low is 1375, if we
talk about the contingencies, then its file is one
thing, it had a pressure and if we
talk about the delivery quantity, then there was two
Lucknow Intercity, it had a pressure, if we
talk in percentage, then there was a delivery of 1627, so let's
talk about the shareholding pattern, the promoters have
59% elasticity, September and dispatch number
and in December, it had
27.1 persons in September, which
increased to 2804 persons in December.  It has become
straight, it has
1326 person shares in September 2010, after cutting one third, it has
12345 per cent stake in the account in December 2019, the
public has 7.5 per cent stake in September 2010,
70 per cent stake in December 2019,
so the
promoter has the highest holding in it, first the
public has 1.2 per cent stake,
so let's talk about financing,
its total profit in September 2020 was
541 crores, which decreased to 452 crores in December, if we
talk about operating profit margin, then it was 102, 147 person shares,
which has reduced to 98% in December, so if we
talk about profit after tax, then the profit explosion
extra fall of 554 crores, which has reduced to
418 crores in December,
this is about net profit  If we talk about it, there was a
net profit of 415 crores in September
which has reduced to a net profit of 30 crores in December, the
decline that was supposed to happen in the profit has been factored in, so if you
want, you can take up this topic as well,
so I hope you
liked the video, you will learn something new from it,
this is not a by state minister,
before taking any position in this channel,
you must consult your financier and we will
meet again in our next video, thank you for
watching